Guide to the Richard White papers SC1323
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Books
  - The Middle Ground: Indians, Empires, and Republics in the Great Lakes Region, 1650-1815
    - Chiefs Authority, 1712 (Box 26, Folder 57)
    - Rotstein (Box 26, Folder 58)
    - High and Mighty Lord, 1936 (Box 26, Folder 59)
  - It's Your Misfortune and None of my Own": A History of the American West.
    - Misfortune revisions - comments, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Turner (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Revisions (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Martin: Paradise of World (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Meinig - Amer. Wests (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - John Modell - Family + fertility on Indiana frontier, 1820 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Kathleen Murphy - Western fictions (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Murphy + Zellner - sequential growth - Labor safety vale doxctrine (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Ohio river backcountry articles, 1989-1990 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Montana's Agony (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Olin Articles, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Pascoe papers, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Robbins (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Rothmann's Jews in West, 1865-1930 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Patty - Billington, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Ralph Mann - Decade After the Gold Rush: social structure in grass valley, 1850-1860 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Jackson Putnam - Turner Thesis + Westward movement (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Domestication + Americanization article (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - The Western (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Mormons - Missouri, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Steve Haebel, 1997 Apr (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Charts test (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Add to text, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Text - C.W., 1979 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - West - random - for text (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Cities, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Sources, Notes, western history lectures part I (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Notes - text (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - recent book West - text (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Genl. Text (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Wishart- fur trade of the American West (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Books - animals (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Don Russell Wild West (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Notes: Back Western article (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - book lists West, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - West History book notes (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Land text note (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Western back test (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - textbook books (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Carstenson notes on books (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Hst. 170 - notes on books added, 1985-1986 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Arrington (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Populism, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Ronda - Exploration, 1760-1815 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - 19th econ, 1840-1880 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - A. E. Addify (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - Ethnic Art, 1880-1980 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Barbara Laslett household structure on American Frontier, 1850 (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - Ostler: Rhetoric of conspiracy (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Gutierrez - Ward, West article, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - Vander Meulin - W Coast, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - Johnson - Bed and board (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - The Organic Machine: The Remaking of the Columbia River
    - Fink + Mitchell papers, 1938 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Wilbert Chapman paper, 1947 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Grand Coulee, 1937-1941 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Floods + flood control, 1948 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Industrial Report N. W. Washington, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Coulee (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Engineering articles on Granf Coulee, 1930s (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - The Columbia + Navigation Mitchell's "Free River" speech Regional Economy + the River, 1886-1955 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Work is Our Joy (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Hydro electric - PNW + California, 1948-1955 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - BPA - Rate increase EIS (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - BPA - General History and Bibliography, 1939 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Norweed - Water Policy, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - CVA: BPA Advisory council report on Columbia valley authority (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - JD Ross - Pricing Electricity (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Robbins - Wlliamette Valley Project (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Dams - Hydro tour, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Columbia River: interstate issues, 1947 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Grand Coulee promo stuff photos, etc, 1947 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Canada - U.S. Treaty: Documents, Negotiations, and the Treaty itself (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Canada - U.S. Treaty: interpretations (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Col. River Treaty, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Columbia Basin inter-agency committee - planning the river + the region, 1948 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Idaho + Montana - farmers (?), 1943 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - BPA Economic Survey of Benton + Franklin Counties (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - BPA: Rates + electricity, 1943 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - Magnuser paper (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - CVA: Reasons and rationale Labor support claimed comparison of BPA + TVA, u1952 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - Nat. Archives (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - Indian Gent. "Mysteries" (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - 6th Grandfather - C. etc. (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Black Elk (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Invented Indian C., 1990 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Creating Iindians Hist.498, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Inventing Indians Reading P., 1991 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - The Bonneville Power Project, 1934-1935 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Grand Coulee and Bonneville Dams, 1935-1937 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Robbins - Narrating Oregon Country (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Gerber - On the Home Front (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - National Archives (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Wesley Dick Visions of Abundance (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Hines - Tenimos, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Elec. For Rural America (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Mumford: Notes (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Neuberger - Conservation, 1941-1944 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Col. Notes - ready, 1991-1992 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Seminar Paper, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Photos Col., 1992 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Bibliography (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Cottrell - Energy Society (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Greenberg - Energy (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Hanford Environmental Dose Reconstruction Project Quarterly Report, 1993- jun (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Hanford Environmental Dose Reconstruction Project Quarterly Report, 1993-sep (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Air Pathway Report Phase I Hanford Environmental Dose Reconstruction Project, 1991-jul (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Hanford Environmental Dose Reconstruction Project Quarterly Report, 1992-dec (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Hanford Environmental Dose Reconstruction Project Quarterly Report, 1993-dec / 1994-feb (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Hanford Environmental Dose Reconstruction Project Quarterly Report, 1992-nov (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Columbia River Pathway Report Phase I of the Hanford Environmental Dose Reconstruction Project, 1991-jul (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Hanford Environmental Dose Reconstruction Project Monthly Report, 1993-jan (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Hanford Environmental Dose Reconstruction Project Monthly Report, 1993-feb (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - Hanford Environmental Dose Reconstruction Project Monthly Report, 1993-mar (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - Hanford Environmental Dose Reconstruction Project Monthly Report, 1993-apr (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - Misc. Notes Col., 1993 (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - Don Hodd: Prophets of Shortage Notes (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - Columbia River Fisheries, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 36)
    - OHS, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 37)
    - Energy, Salmon and Labor - Revised (Box 28, Folder 38)
    - Energy: Background Col., 1972 (Box 28, Folder 39)
    - Energy + Social Transformation Articles from 1920 - 1940's ( The Survey ), 1920-1945 (Box 28, Folder 40)
    - Sci. American, 1930-oct. (Box 28, Folder 41)
    - When Dams Weren't Damned Article, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 42)
    - Notes Books: Hunter: Water Power (Box 28, Folder 43)
    - Geomorphology etc., 1968 (Box 28, Folder 44)
    - Willingham - Cascade Locks, 1876-1896 (Box 28, Folder 45)
    - Flushing Times and Polution by Neal, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 46)
    - Siegel: Energy Concept, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 47)
    - Oregon State Engineers Office: Power, 1912 (Box 28, Folder 48)
    - Columbia: Navigation, 1913 (Box 28, Folder 49)
    - Magnussen Papers, 1920's (Box 28, Folder 50)
    - Hoover - National Policy (Box 28, Folder 51)
    - America's Power Resources Chester Gilbert Joseph Pogue, 1921 (Box 28, Folder 52)
    - Washington State Grange - Attitudes toward electric power (Box 28, Folder 53)
    - Columbia - River Mile Index, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 54)
    - Rivers - General, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 55)
    - Woods, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 56)
    - Rufus Woods (Box 28, Folder 57)
    - Rufus Woods Collection - U. W. (Box 28, Folder 58)
    - Rufus Woods, 1931-1934 (Box 28, Folder 59)
    - Carl Magnuson, 1935 (Box 28, Folder 60)
    - Batchellor Willis, 1921-1933 (Box 28, Folder 61)
    - Headwaters of Col. Idaho, 1895 (Box 28, Folder 62)
    - Mchouglin Letters notes (Box 28, Folder 63)
    - Lewis Clark, 1806 (Box 28, Folder 64)
    - Palmer Journal, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 65)
    - OHS M. (Box 28, Folder 66)
  - Remembering Ahanagran: A History of Stories
    - Ahanagran Leffs (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Ahanagran 2, 1995-2000 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Sun Belt, 1987 Dec (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Politics, 1969-1980 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Econ dev. West (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Social Conflied, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - As - H. st, 1865-1900 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - T. notes (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Frontier Social History (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Social, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - 19th Century - Cultural/ Social (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - 20th Century Social (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Women, 1981-1985 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Mobility + Opportunity - 19th century West, 1975-1977 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Labor, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Boltan: Geo of Health (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Public land, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Nebraska Capital (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Misc. articles - Indians (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Vigilante, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Articles: Peter David, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Farasher: More Motley (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Patty - Smithsonian, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Limerick: Hawaii, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Kleppnen "Politics without Prties: the Western states unpub. Paper, 1900-1984 (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - Migration to Frontier John Hudsen, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - Hardesty, 1980-1981 (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - Hijiya Response (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - Gutierrez - Sin Frenterey (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - David G. - Significant to Cohen (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - Ramon G. - Understanding Hispanic Per., 1988 (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - Gutierrez - "Sin Fronteras" (Box 36, Folder 32)
    - 19th Pol. Graebner Mex. Wa (Box 36, Folder 33)
    - Goetzmann - Mountain Man as Jacksonian May (Box 36, Folder 34)
    - Easterber Peter's Article (Box 36, Folder 35)
    - DeGraff. Black Women (Box 36, Folder 36)
    - Sarah Deutsch: Women Intercultural Relations (Box 36, Folder 37)
    - Courtwright: Disease and Disorder on Amer. Frontier, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 38)
    - Carter + Spencer - Stereotypes of the Mountain man (Box 36, Folder 39)
    - Ian Bogue - Social Theory and the Pioneer, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 40)
    - Robert Bieder: Kinship as a factor in Migration (Box 36, Folder 41)
    - Boden hamer - Law + Disorder an Early Frontier, 1919 (Box 36, Folder 42)
    - Aron: Lessons in Conquest (Box 36, Folder 43)
    - New Deal Arrington, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 44)
    - Abbott - Regional History (Box 36, Folder 45)
    - New Western History Turner - Critical Theory (Box 36, Folder 46)
    - Newspapers, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 47)
    - Misc. popular west (Box 36, Folder 48)
    - Nebraska Capital, 1863 (Box 36, Folder 49)
    - National Museum of the American Indian, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 50)
    - Capt. Jack (Box 36, Folder 51)
    - Robinson - Western myth, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 52)
    - Bozeman Material, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 53)
    - Diary of Sutter (Box 36, Folder 54)
    - Davis (Box 36, Folder 55)
    - Satter Talk (Box 36, Folder 56)
    - Draft rewrite A F (Box 36, Folder 57)
    - West - New Repable - K. + Freemer, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 58)
    - Smith, Cheoviowith, Stockman, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 59)
    - Conrad Burns Bic, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 60)
    - Bills - Public lands, etc. (Box 36, Folder 61)
    - Western states: Taxes, reviews, etc., 1991 (Box 36, Folder 62)
    - National Press: Treatment: Weirdness in West, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 63)
    - Initiative, Referendum, Recalls (Box 36, Folder 64)
    - General stats: states (Box 36, Folder 65)
    - Paper WHA, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 66)
    - Journal of American History, 1996 Jun (Box 36, Folder 67)
    - Morrisey:Western Historical Quarterly, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 68)
    - Hispanic Water Lavin S.C., 1994 (Box 36, Folder 69)
    - WHA, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 70)
    - Dening Seneca Possessed (Box 36, Folder 71)
    - Sabin: Home Abroad (Box 36, Folder 72)
    - Mitchell - NWH + Landscape, 1998 (Box 36, Folder 73)
    - Rothman - Wichita, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 74)
    - Gutierez - Chicano History, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 75)
    - Casteneda Frontiers Article, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 76)
    - Race relation, 1900-1937 (Box 36, Folder 77)
    - Racial + Ethnic, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 78)
    - Books for A.Quarterly, 1890-1930 (Box 36, Folder 79)
    - Vander Meusen West Coast Aircraft Labor, 1935-1941 (Box 36, Folder 80)
    - Worster: Canada, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 81)
    - Elliott West article, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 82)
    - Alan Taylor - Col. Frontier, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 83)
    - Lee Soltono - Land Inequality Ohio - Tenn., 1981 (Box 36, Folder 84)
    - Shortridge - Frontier's influence voter turnout, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 85)
    - Ginsy Scharff. Mobility (Box 36, Folder 86)
    - Zeyde - Pardon file, 1931 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - My grandfather's trial + appeal Ahanagran, 1926-1928 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Sources - M's book, 1972-1986 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - notes - misc. Ireland, 1911 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Xeroxes - Mom's book, 1942 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Ireland - Marriage + Birth certificate, 1870-1873 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Xeroxes: Folklore, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - American wake (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Notes: tapes (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Ireland, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Xeroxes from Maggie birth/marriage certificates, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Tait Material, 1941 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Sgt. Mulvihill, 1916-1919 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Chicago research, 1907-1955 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Phillpott - Slums Phette, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Source on Ireland Janet Wolan Loyola (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Sources - Ireh, 1919-1921 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Ireland - Libraries, corr., 1995 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Railroaded: The Transcontinentals and the Making of Modern America
    - Laconia (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Residential Chicago: Chicago Land Use Survey (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Chicago, 1930 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Sifton - Changing, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - John Walsh: Immigration, passport, 1928 (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - photocopy request, 1934 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Southwest News, 1934-1938 (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - Burgess papers (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - Chicago Laws, 1938 (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - Mom: immigration interview (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - Similar books, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 29)
    - 1940 (Box 37, Folder 30)
    - Union Leader (Box 37, Folder 31)
    - Federation news, 1936 (Box 37, Folder 32)
    - Notes: Mozart St. (Box 37, Folder 33)
    - Chicago Material, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 34)
    - Golden Jubilee (Box 37, Folder 35)
    - Grace Neville: articles, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 36)
    - Kirby Miller (Box 37, Folder 37)
    - Kennelly: O'Conner of Carrigafoyle (Box 37, Folder 38)
    - Lewis Topographical Dictionary of Ireland (Box 37, Folder 39)
    - IRA: Bally to Kath (Box 37, Folder 40)
    - Financial aid Irish - seconds, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 41)
    - Blunt: Land War in Ireland, 1923 (Box 37, Folder 42)
    - Writings, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 43)
    - Midway, 1939 (Box 37, Folder 44)
    - Trinity Estates, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 45)
    - William Walsh: Registry of Deeds (Box 37, Folder 46)
    - Margaret Mary, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 47)
    - Chaps 1-3 (Box 37, Folder 48)
    - Moun new (citizenship etc), 1969 (Box 37, Folder 49)
    - John Walsh: Chicago Residence, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 50)
    - Kerry's Fighting Story, 1916-1921 (Box 37, Folder 51)
    - Edie's letter, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 52)
    - Zeyde - trial, 1928 (Box 37, Folder 53)
    - Dad - Harverey, 1936-1940 (Box 37, Folder 54)
    - Boston Pols - Notes, 1932-1987 (Box 37, Folder 55)
    - Calendars, 1796-2025 (Box 37, Folder 56)
    - Ireland letters, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 57)
    - Answers to Questions, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 58)
    - Dad - Discharge papers, 1953 (Box 37, Folder 59)
    - Immigration laws, 1925 (Box 37, Folder 60)
    - Massachusetts for book, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 61)
    - Rhino (Box 37, Folder 62)
    - Mort, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 63)
    - Hillel - Mishlean Tetila (Box 37, Folder 64)
    - Maud Murry, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 65)
    - Mom: War years (Box 37, Folder 66)
    - St. Ritas, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 67)
    - Letters - comments on manuscripts, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 68)
    - Contact: dad, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 69)
    - Notes: Bert. Edie, 1943 (Box 37, Folder 70)
    - Dad: Harvard, Boston L., 1940 (Box 37, Folder 71)
    - Boston Latin, Dorchester, etc., 1996 (Box 37, Folder 72)
    - Harvard visit, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 73)
    - Chauncey letter, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 74)
    - Mail and files division (Box 37, Folder 75)
    - Mom - late corrections + letter (Box 37, Folder 76)
    - Mom's letters, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 77)
    - Notes: Ireland tapes Irish + Jews misc., 1995 (Box 37, Folder 78)
    - Ireland letters (Box 37, Folder 79)
    - Mom's parents - death notices - letter (Box 37, Folder 80)
    - Mom - second batch + passport, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 81)
    - Nat. library (Box 37, Folder 82)
    - Correspondence, Records, etc., 1996-1997 (Box 37, Folder 83)
    - Ahanagran Maps (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - James Livingston - Social Analysis, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - National integration, 1860-1920 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Grodinsky, transcontinental RR states (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Orsi - SP, 1875-1930 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Mark Hopkins, 1881 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - A Fast Life RR wrote (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Riegel Western RR Pods, 1931 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Petrsky Neoclassical Advent, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Destler - Western Radicalism, 1944 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Arnesen: Banquo's Ghost, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Gutmen: Protestantism + American Labor, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Gagan: Perkins, RR + public, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Articles: Chinese, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Trollope: North America, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Ichioka: Jap. Labor Contractors, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Readers Corporate corrupts, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Business + Radical Reconstruction, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Gavin Wright- Critique, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Gordon Chang - Korea case CA-RR, 2000 Nov (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Central Finance Co. Carmen, Mueller, 1927 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Farnham - Weakend Study, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Haber - New Ind. Econ, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Haorwitz- Transformation of American Law, 1870-1960 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Huntington Conkly Article, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Fletcher Green credit mobilizer, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Sam Truett: RRs, 1903 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Lise's paper - RRs, 1999 Jun (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - RD's Bonnes Diss., 1998 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Circus - Virginia city, 1870 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Circus - SLC, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Circus, 1869 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Klein - Up, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Klein - study of Big Business (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - John Murran Corruptor (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Summers party games, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Summers- to make the wheels revolve we must have grease, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Mark Wilgan Mil econ, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Wiesle - Fran desert Exposition, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Public documents - RR (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Library notice, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Archives slips (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Archival sources, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Federal Court records - RR, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - PA Historical Society, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - RR + A's, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - Western - ft.Wats, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - Library, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Charts (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - RR notes- book (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - St. Laws (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Berkeley emails, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - Xerox sheets - villard papers, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - Xerox sheets - Stanford, 1987-2001 (Box 14, Folder 53)
    - Mahl papers, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 54)
    - Huntington Orders (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - Stanford archives xerox (Box 14, Folder 56)
    - Hagley (Box 14, Folder 57)
    - Sources = RR (Box 14, Folder 58)
    - Dasset Chap of SP, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 59)
    - Articles RR aid + finances, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 60)
    - Articles- Cal RR + Politics, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 61)
    - Nash. Reagan Bill, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 62)
    - Nash. - Cal. R.R. Comm., 1962 Mar (Box 14, Folder 63)
    - Berk Whose Aubris (Box 14, Folder 64)
    - Johnson + Supple- boston capitalists (Box 14, Folder 65)
    - Development of financial markets (Box 14, Folder 66)
    - Gilchrist - Fink and pooling, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 67)
    - Railroad Land Development etc. (Box 14, Folder 68)
    - Principles of RR Transporters, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 69)
    - Lamoreaux - reframing the past, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 70)
    - Determinants - Ute (Box 14, Folder 71)
    - Termini (Box 14, Folder 72)
    - Frank Leonard - Terminus (Box 14, Folder 73)
    - CPR + Vancouver (Box 14, Folder 74)
    - Race collateral credit (Box 14, Folder 75)
    - Gregory Thompson, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 76)
    - Seligman, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 77)
    - Tom Scott - Civil War, 1940 (Box 14, Folder 78)
    - Huntington outgoing, 1884-1885 (Box 14, Folder 79)
    - Xerox, 1887 May - Dec (Box 14, Folder 80)
    - John Gardner, 1888 Jan - Dec (Box 14, Folder 81)
    - CPH, 1888-1889 (Box 14, Folder 82)
    - CPH incoming, 1891 Jan - Juy (Box 14, Folder 83)
    - CPH, 1891 Aug - Dec (Box 14, Folder 84)
    - Xerox, 1889 Jan - Jul (Box 14, Folder 85)
    - CPH, 1889 Jul - Dec (Box 14, Folder 86)
    - Clyde, Thomas Knight, 1877-1878 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - CP Politics Julian, 1873 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Colbuon (RSC) (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Sherill - sinking feed, 1876-1880 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Boyd corr. Lobbying, 1873-1880 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Cong. Genl., 1879 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Pol favors, 1872-1873 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Conbly to CPH, 1879 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Friends of CP (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - McCortele etc. Payoff lobbying CP, 1877-1879 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Politics AA Sargent, 1872-1874 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - C.P. politics - CA, 1876-1879 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - West to Huntington US Senate, 1876-1878 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Ferry, 1879 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Passes + favors, 1878 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - CA opposition to fending bills, 1890s (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Stephen White - S.I.P. CA pol., 1890s (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Politics - Conness, 1870-1875 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - S.P. routes, 1875-1876 (Box 18, Folder 19)